Many of my videos will be
on health insurance where I tell you
what you should check before taking health insurance. I will do
0.5 inch from one side and
f-18
suicide
suhaag. So
subscribe
button, there are some
important things for college, some things are more important for you, we will
talk about that,
subscribe and like, comment, what are those
things that are
most important for you after taking the policy, that you need to see, that you need to
check, United
Maharashtra Committee, horoscope of time votes,
economic policy, Sattu, policy document, that is why it is
not happening,
requested, open the policy document, at this
time you have got long-term
depression by tossing, it is automatically
important that you are Mormon, it is very important for you to
know that there is
something wrong in the joint, if you come to know about China then
you will be helpless, so
many people, it is a matter, so we will talk about what you need to check,
first
is your basic details, that is absolutely
basic details, like we have your
professor's name, address, phone number, email ID, the
property is written in such a way that  It is not there
and you must have set it double in the application form
but if there is any typing mistake then it can happen
many times at
any stage, check the sweater distance and
after that how many
installed members are there in your policy and the
name date of birth of all of them, there is
no need to make any changes in this, I am
telling you one thing here because this
endorsement is done by Guava, if you
take this form and the information is wrong in the policy
then it is necessary to select it and if you
check it there itself then there will be
no problem in future, so these things you should check whether the date
of birth is wrong or the name is not wrong,
spelling correction, then you have to fill all these
things in the basic details of the tractor
plant, your material is totaly, then to turn his
ride, if you are interested, no my friend,
for international then there should be integration
so that the total is always and want the next
subscribe point,
you should make proper use of the medical information of Mathura,
you filled it on the application form, please
tell me the settings inside your tele screening  I have got my test done and told you there too
but it is possible that there may be corruption in polish removal
so it is important for you to decide whether the
information is optional or not. The
member who went to Salman's care also has
four such cases if there are quality end members then there is
medical history also but that middle
last quite possibly the place of possession is
not wrong, that is to say touch the property, every
branch of Shekhar will go through the entire process with hard work, then
this point will not be
entered in your display, please the medical
admission you told that the property is mentioned,
one thing is reaction that did I not say anything in
which there is a shark slide anywhere,
you should not have any problem in class, so this is
another thing I have just seen in solitaire,
these mistakes are happening in the case of portability,
whenever someone got a call about the
silver lining that our policy survey was
from last year but I
took the neck of last year old cars from according to inch, then
one year
portability was written there, so it means that
some of your meetings are clear,
policy Mahmood, we have 10 minutes on the wicket of the year  I had to
call Vikas, the date posted was wrong,
so please share the date you have
given for the Italian property
in the application form, then check the portability
website to see if the date of function of quality is
correct or not. Secondly, if you
go to the policy from time to time, suppose you already have a
cost of two lakhs, or if you are opting
for the last policy, then the previous policy has always been carried forward, if the
property has been gifted, then that
number should be carried forward by 3 lakhs because the
supervisory employee who has been through you, then
you should also check that the
printer has always been gifted the property, but at that
time the next very important point is that no
one else can do this, here
you have your emergency contact person,
but if it is the real mother, then
who is the emergency point for your family, if it is in the
form of any of your advisors, then their
name and contact number should be mentioned, you
can put a video on the emergency file or policy, you
can share their contact number, this
number should be in the phone of the family members,
whose physical number should also be in the phone,
instead of surgical  Also,
write down Sarup Singh's name and number and leave it. If there is an
emergency, these 10 people will have to
suffer the time platform. The
skin of the times, the wheel rim of the
lord of all family members,
so ghee and got admitted. I don't know
which policy is there, where is the qualification,
which room will be available. This question
comes up. If there is a celebrity in this, then if you have
any emergency contact person and
false teeth on that central school, their Rover, if they get
reduced then the number is second
semester. I would also suggest that
your fennel comes to the office very much. What is its real,
very soft copy. Saathiya
drama officer service intake is not there, then it
depends on Vishuddha Chakra. Take a printout and
you can make a soft copy of it into a file.
Subah Tiwari, Abhinav is not able to make an effort to
select the password. If you have set
thousands of passwords through your face recognition,
you do not know the medal hope, then it is
actually a superhit printout,
with such a place, the marriage number knows
that here  Expenses and this point, so
above that, the name and number of the emergency contact person,
solid, we do not have any dish appointment
and can easily get in
touch in a smooth manner. Now last but not the least
policy hardening was on the head. At this time, that
policy document comes with it, there is
also a polygraphic for details, regarding this,
go through it because it happens,
whereas in the voice of the Chief Minister,
this point was not told in his voice, but
yourself, there you feel that I am taking
these notes of this site and you have
selected from this, that will happen only when first you
open your policy and check it, then
you feel that it happens like this, after a long time, in
reality, it needs to be cancelled,
okay, first you have done a lot of research, there is
no harm in doing a big horse, if you have come, then please
keep all these things in mind and even after taking the policy, it
is equally important to see all this as much as to
know before taking it, I would
like to like and share a lot of what happens to
me.  Inquiry from Sim Lodha about
getting health insurance I've been researching for six months
or subscribing to Olive 10 years strong does that
mean you're
thinking about it then go for it it does
n't mean you'll find a policy of never getting one
buy it all and
talk to someone I'm coming in foreign
policy but I've had
this red chilli for weeks udaigarh please don't wait you don't
know what will happen if there is
any such medical emergency in future such help
complex then you won't
get the policy pure silk best example from
roti kapda and makaan sur roti kapda makaan
and insurance the basic necessities suit don't
loose right now don't do it for family
because it will be wrong next airport do
depression so take it means for
artificial meetings in my office
poster of light which unites that process
220 don't just do it don't get into which destroy
suggestions earn side if there is anything like this you
would like to give to your character that worry
tell me in the comment section from
which laxative make please tell  Or
and also you should share your experience if
you feel like it because such an appointment has been
mixed, your mind should be
kept in quality square, so instead of the back,
we should direct the crowd of devotees towards anger, Bhringraj Sonam
is from Miding and now any reminder, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then
please subscribe also, all most
intense, it has happened, Lord and
Mrs.
[Music]
do it
[Music] it has happened,
that a do it
[Music]
do it